反對嘅請舉手。
Mr. President, in my capacity,
to examine the subsidiary legislation.
and report its deliberations to the House Committee.
With these remarks, President, I urge members to support the motion.
在The House Committee Meeting held on fifth October two thousand and one eight.
I move that the motion under my name, as printed on the agenda, be passed.
成員決定要成立一個小委員會，來審查子委員會的立法。
現在嘅代議議題係梁繼昌原動議嘅議案，予以通過。是否有議員想發言？
兩部分在席議員分別過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。
現在嘅代決議題係梁繼昌議員動議嘅議案，予以通過，贊成嘅請舉手。
thus the committee held a meeting on 19th October 2018 with the administration.
議員議案根據基本法第七十三條第五項及第十項動議嘅議案。
我認為議題係獲得功能團體選舉產生同埋分區直接選舉產生嘅兩部分在職議員分別以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。
to allow sufficient time for the subcommittee to consider the supplementary information provided by the administration pursuant to members' request made at the meeting.
我 call upon members to support the motion on extending the period for scrutinising the subsidiary legislation to 28 November 2018.
作為主席，就這兩項命令，根據《內地税收條例》第49/1A條所訂的命令，於14月14日刊憲。
第二項議案延展於二零一八年十月十日提交本會審覽嘅兩項有關税務條例嘅附屬法例嘅修訂期限，我請梁繼昌議員發言及動議議案。